

ADHE AKRAM AZHARI

DATA MANAGEMENT & UI/UX DESIGNER



ABOUT ME

I am an Informatics undergraduate at Telkom University who has an interest in working in Data Management and UI/UX Designer. I have good skills in doing data analysis, visualizing user flow into a tested and beautiful product design, and able to operate several software such as Figma, HTML, CSS, PHP, C, C++, Python, Mysql, and Sql. Through my experience and skills, I am ready to make a positive contribution to the company.



CONTACT



+62 822 9379 3000



adheakram09@gmail.com



@ adheakram_



in Adhe Akram Azhari



JI Teluk Mekongg, Komp. Antam, Kolaka Regency, South East Sulawesi



SKILLS

- Communication
- Time Management
- Teamwork
- Discipline
- Critical Thinking
- Attention To Details



WORKING EXPERIENCES

DATA MANAGEMENT / April 2024 - Present ANTAM TBK, KOLAKA REGENCY

- Analyze data related to vehicle turnover containing mining production.
- Analyzed the scale of vehicles containing mining production (Gross, Tare and Netto).



WORK TRAINING

UI/UX DESIGNER / September 2023

BY JAYJAY

Learn how to design a product or application in accordance with the terms and conditions of design, and learn the use of figma in design, and spreadsheets and mazes to design user experience.



INTERNSHIP EXPERIENCES

WEB ANALYST / October 2022 - November 2022 OFFICE TELKOM UNIVERSITY, BANDUNG REGENCY

- Responsible for carrying out research and community service activities.
- Develop research centers and collaborative projects with external parties.
- Analyze a PPM website regarding what the website lacks in terms of content, appearance and others.

DATA MANAGEMENT / July 2018 - September 2018 TELKOM INDONESIA, YOGYAKARTA

- Taking care of indihome customer data such as entering data on customers who have just registered or are currently running.
- Collaborating with people in the field to open the port in ODP so that the port can connect to the internet.



EDUCATION

TELKOM UNIVERSITY / 2019 - 2023

BACHELOR OF INFORMATICS

Obtained the S.Kom degree with a final GPA of 3.60

TELKOM VOCATIONAL HIGH SCHOOL MAKASSAR / 2016 - 2019 COMPUTER & NETWORK ENGINEERING

National Exam average final score 91.31



SOFTWARE

- MICROSOFT OFFICE
- HTML, CSS, PHP, C, C++, PYTHON
- ADOBE PHOTOSHOP
- MYSOL
- FIGMA
- SQL



ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCE

TRAINER/ATHLETE / October 2019 - December 2022

TELKOM UNIVERSITY BADMINTON CLUB

- Providing material to fellow members regarding how to play badminton
- Participated in badminton competitions representing the campus.



WORKSHOP EXPERIENCES

INTERNAL SEMINAR / Februari 2023

BY TELKOM UNIVERSITY

Became a speaker and raised the topic of my final project which is detecting hate speech on Instagram comments using the RoBERTa method.